g2play.net 2018-10-21

# Privacy Policy

**G2PLAY.net respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data. We realize that the exciting growth of the Internet and online services raise questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our long-standing commitment of safeguarding privacy to our online and Internet activities.**

In addition to this general online privacy policy, you may receive notice of other terms that apply to particular promotions or services. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

G2PLAY.net does not share, disclose or sell any personally-identifiable information (such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address) collected online on G2PLAY.net' sites with other unaffiliated companies or organizations for non-G2PLAY.net marketing purposes. Because this information is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding. G2PLAY.net also does not market to, or knowingly collect personal information from, children under he age of 13 on Company sites. 

**How We Use Information**

G2PLAY.net uses the personally-identifiable information we collect online principally to provide you with the service(s) you have ordered and to let you know about other offerings which may be of interest to you. Postal and e-mail address information, for example, enables communication about services offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services. 

We also provide personally-identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with G2PLAY.net' services, or with our customers' or others' use of them. 

**How We Collect Information**

G2PLAY.net collects information online by asking you for it, for example, when you order a service, apply for a job, or respond to a survey, offer or other promotion. A customer's name, address (postal and e-mail) and telephone number are the most important pieces of information, but we might request other information, based on, for example, the service(s) being ordered or promoted. 

G2PLAY.net may also use "cookies" and similar technology to obtain information about your visits to our sites or your responses to e-mail from us - both individually and in aggregated data that does not identify you. These reporting tools tell us the parts of our web sites or e-mails in which you showed an interest or took some action, and help us improve the quality and usefulness of our sites.   
Security

We may provide your personal data including personally-identifiable information to our service providers to support the operation of the Site and our services, in particular such personal data may be transferred to our service providers who will use it to detect whether you have ever committed fraud, been an accessory to such a crime or have attempted any of the same. If so, we shall be entitled to refuse to provide you with our services. By accepting this Privacy Policy you agree that our service providers will compile such personal data and any results of such detection into a database by automated means and that your personal data will be accessible by other customers of our service providers, who may require it for the prevention and detection of fraud in the event of your use of such other customer’s services. At any time, you may request details of the personal data that our service providers hold about you.

**We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the G2PLAY.net's web site you will need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information.  **
